potterybarn.ca 2006-06-20

# Pottery Barn Canada

|  |  |  We are part of "Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands" which includes Williams-Sonoma, Pottery Barn, pottery barn kids, PBteen, west elm, Chambers and Hold Everything. Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (the phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our web sites, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, the information. This policy applies only to users accessing our web site from Canada.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands support and adhere to the guidelines and practices adopted by the CSA Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information, which forms a part of the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. Among other things, we have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale or exchange with other marketers; (2) honour customers' requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (3) honour customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands.

See the Following Topics:  
Collecting Information About You  
Using Information About You  
Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You  
Protecting Children  
Cookies  
Security  
Links to Third Party Sites  
Policy Changes  
Your Feedback

**Collecting Information About You**  
In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, register to receive catalogues, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) at which we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. We also maintain a record of your online product purchases. Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web site. We will maintain your personally identifiable information for five years after your last transaction.

**Using Information About You**  
We use the personally identifiable information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands. From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Select Partners. In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including personally identifiable information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, in our stores or through our catalogues. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Select Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands or to others. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it.

**Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You**  
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us or from our Select Partners please let us know by writing to us at Database Management, Marketing Services Department, Williams-Sonoma, Inc. 3250 Van Ness Avenue, San Francisco, CA 94109 or by sending an [email](mailto:privacy@wsgc.com) to our Privacy Officer. Please be sure to include your email address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. We try to keep all information which we collect accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you would like to update or correct your email address, street address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.

Please note that these requests may take some time to be effective, particularly if we are removing your name from postal mailings. In addition, when you purchase from us online or through our catalogs, or when you choose to enter a sweepstakes or other promotion, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive communications.

Please remember, if you delete certain information you may not be able to continue to purchase products or access other portions of our web site without entering additional information. If you have questions about this privacy policy, please [email](mailto:privacy@wsgc.com) our Privacy Officer by clicking here.

**Protecting Children**  
Williams-Sonoma, Inc. Brands take special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our web sites are general audience sites. We do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web.

**Cookies**  
Our web sites use "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at their stores and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyzing your visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our Service Providers.

**Security**  
We use sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your personal information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will do our best to protect its security on our systems.

We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

**Links to Third Party Sites**  
Our web sites may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.

**Policy Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. This policy was posted in April 2003.

**Your Feedback**  
To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may [email](mailto:privacy@wsgc.com) us.
